IBT0020
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Audio and Video collection
1933-1968
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT0020
19.5 Linear Feet UP Boxes 1-13
bib #
skeletal bib # 11487748 MMS ID# 99114877483604107
- Audiotapes, 1959 - 1967; Series 1; 1 Linear Feet One Record Center box.
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of audio tapes for various IBT events such as National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, Drive Essay winners, and an interview with James R. Hoffa between 1959 - 1967.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged numerically by RT designation.
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, RT-202 Reel 2 of 11, 21 February - 3 March, 1967; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, RT-202 Reel 3 of 11, 21 February - 3 March, 1967; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, RT-202 Reel 4 of 11, 21 February - 3 March, 1967; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, RT-202 Reel 5 of 11, 21 February - 3 March, 1967; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, RT-202 Reel 6 of 11, 21 February - 3 March, 1967; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, RT-202 Reel 7 of 11, 21 February - 3 March, 1967; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, RT-202 Reel 8 of 11, 21 February - 3 March, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, RT-202 Reel 9 of 11, 21 February - 3 March, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, RT-202 Reel 10 of 11, 21 February - 3 March, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations, RT-202 Reel 11 of 11, 21 February - 3 March, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Drive Essay Contest Winners RT-203 Reel 1 of 2, 6 July, 2 August 1965 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Drive Essay Contest Winners RT-203 Reel 2 of 2, 6 July, 2 August 1965 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Mechanics Contract Negotiations Report RT-204, 13 November, 1964; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - A Short Interview with James R. Hoffa RT-205, February 1962; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Testimony Before the House Labor Committee RT-206, Reels 1-4 of 6, 9 June, 1959; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Testimony Before the House Labor Committee RT-206 Reels 5-6 of 6, 9, June, 1959; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations RT-207 Reel 1 of 10, 8-14 February, 1967; Series 1 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations RT-207 Reel 2 of 10, 8-14 February, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations RT-207 Reel 3 of 10, 8-14 February, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations RT-207 Reel 4 of 10, 8-14 February, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations RT-207 Reel 5 of 10, 8-14 February, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations RT-207 Reel 6 of 10, 8-14 February, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations RT-207 Reel 7 of 10, 8-14 February, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations RT-207 Reel 8 of 10, 8-14 February, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations RT-207 Reel 9 of 10, 8-14 February, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - National Master Freight Agreement Negotiations RT-207 Reel 10 of 10, 8-14 February, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 26)